#### Contact

2nd population group, Thachha town, Hatinh, Vietnam 84984348464 (Mobile) hongmienft98@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/emsnguyen98 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Java Web Development Spring Framework Angular

### Languages

Chinese (Limited Working)
English (Full Professional)
Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

# Mien Nguyen

time-obsessive

## Summary

I major in Software Engineering and I am yearning to become a fullstack web developer.

At high school, I was specialized in English and have been an English tutor ever since. I love learning and teaching languages as a whole.

Cristiano Ronaldo and Steve Jobs have always been my two big idols, one for his hard work and persistence and another for his creativity and uniqueness.

## Experience

FPT University
Student
September 2016 - Present
Study Software Engineering

dungbocuoc.com Translator September 2014 - Present Study

## Education

**FPT University** 

Master's degree, Software Engineering · (2016 - 2020)

freeCodeCamp

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (2016 - 2017)

Hatinh high school for the gifted

English · (2013 - 2016)

Phan Huy Chu Secondary School

· (2013 - 2016)